Office of Analytical Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Director's correspondence, 1968 - 1991; F-52-1; 25 cm of textual records
  - Semester system, 1971 - 1980; F-52-1-0-0-150 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.10.2.
  - Modification of summer semester, 1974 - 1976; F-52-1-0-0-151 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.10.2.1.
  - Calendar year operation, 1970 - 1974; F-52-1-0-0-152 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.10.3.
  - Teaching [and] research semester analysis, 1972; F-52-1-0-0-153 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.10.4.
  - University reviews (academic - non-academic), 1975 - 1980; F-52-1-0-0-154 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.10.5.
  - Induced work load matrix, 1981; F-52-1-0-0-155 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.10.6.
  - Univeristy - role, mission, planning, 1980 - 1981; F-52-1-0-0-156 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.10.8.
  - Systems, 1972 - 1981; F-52-1-0-0-157 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.11.
  - Computer assisted instruction, 1970 - 1975; F-52-1-0-0-158 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.11.1.
  - Systems contracting, 1978 - 1979; F-52-1-0-0-159 (Archival box - standard 52-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.11.2.
  - Provincial University data base, 1981; F-52-1-0-0-160 (Archival box - standard 52-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.11.4.
  - Graduate students, 1981; F-52-1-0-0-161 (Archival box - standard 52-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.11.8.
  - Registrar, 1981 - 1982; F-52-1-0-0-162 (Archival box - standard 52-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.11.9.
  - Pre-registration and student course infromation systems, 1980; F-52-1-0-0-163 (Archival box - standard 52-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.11.9.1.
  - Tuition fee proposals and data, vol. 1, 1977 - 1981; F-52-1-0-0-164 (Archival box - standard 52-19)
    Open
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.12.1.
  - Tuition fee proposals and data, vol. 2, 1977 - 1981; F-52-1-0-0-165 (Archival box - standard 52-19)
  - Tuition fees, 1980 - 1982; F-52-1-0-0-166 (Archival box - standard 52-19)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.12.2.
- Enrollment research, 1970 - 1991; F-52-2; 12 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records arising from research in the area of post secondary school enrollment. Series includes statistics and committee records.
  Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - B.C. Post Secondary Education Enrollment Forecasting Committee, 1971 - 1976; F-52-2-1; 4 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records of the B.C. Post Secondary Education Enrollment Forecasting Committee. Subseries includes correspondence, memoranda, and meeting agendas and minutes.
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1971; F-52-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1972; F-52-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1973; F-52-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1974; F-52-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1975; F-52-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1976; F-52-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
  - SFU enrollment statistics, 1970 - 1991; F-52-2-2; 8 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of SFU enrollment statistics, by semester. Subseries also includes some memoranda.
    - SFU Enrollment Statistics, 1970 - 1978; F-52-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1979; F-52-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1980; F-52-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1981; F-52-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1982; F-52-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1983; F-52-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1984; F-52-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1985; F-52-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1986; F-52-2-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1987; F-52-2-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1988; F-52-2-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1989; F-52-2-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1990; F-52-2-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
    - Semester Enrollments, 1991; F-52-2-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 52-3)
- General statistical studies, 1965 - 1993; F-52-3; 49 cm of textual records
  Series consists of various statistical studies and surveys created by the Analytical Studies office, as well as studies prepared by various other offices before the establishment of the Analytical Studies office. Series includes faculty salary surveys; SFU enrollment predictions; enrollment statistics of high school and regional colleges; statistics regarding operating costs, sabbatical leaves, tuition fees; alumni employment surveys; grade point average statistics; and other studies.
  - Faculty Statistics, 1966 - 1980; F-52-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - Faculty salary survey, 1966 - 1967; F-52-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salary survey, 1967 - 1968; F-52-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - Faculty salary survey, 1968 - 1969; F-52-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - Faculty salary survey, 1969 - 1970; F-52-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - Faculty salary survey, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - Faculty salary survey, 1971 - 1972; F-52-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - salaries of teaching staff at Can. Univ. Publication, 1965 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - salary scales report data, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - pension survey, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salary increases, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Enrollment projection, 1972 - 1973; F-52-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Enrollment reports received - a listing, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Enrollment projections to 1981, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Enrollment predictions to 1985/86, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty hired and terminated from 1965, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
    Restricted in whole
  - Faculty listing including leaves of absence, January, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty listing including leaves of absence, Fall, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty listing including leaves of absence, Fall, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty listing, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty pattern of teaching and research, 1965 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Copy of faculty personal information card, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty promotions from 1966, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty resources, use of, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salaries, 1966 - 1967; F-52-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salary increases, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salary increases (Head count average merit increases and rank, step designation), 1969 - 1970; F-52-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salary averages by rank and dept., 1970; F-52-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salary comparisons SFU and UBC, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 52-4)
  - Faculty salary review department submission, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary increases, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary increases, 1968; F-52-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary listing, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salaries - medians by rank, 1967; F-52-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary review Directions and Foundation material, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary review Directions and Foundation material, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Dominion Bureau of Statistics - faculty salary survey, 1965 - 1966; F-52-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary statistics, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary statistics, 1971 - 1972; F-52-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary by rank, 1967 - 1970; F-52-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary printouts in various groupings, 1968 - 1969; F-52-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary statistics, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Faculty salary survey, 1968 - 1969; F-52-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - FTE enrollment by academic years, 1965 - 1970; F-52-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - High school enrollment in BC from, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Leaves of absence, fiscal year, 1969 - 1970; F-52-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Librarians' salary review, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Minor code description, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - National Research Council - surveys and publications, 1965 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development survey of universities, 1969 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Operating costs re student credit hours, 1969 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Credit/no credit grading system, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 52-5)
  - Day research bureau - survey, 1968; F-52-3-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Personnel policies and procedures, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Previous teaching careers SFU faculty; tenure listings, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - PSA faculty salary history to, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Professional Development Centre Enrollments, staff, salaries and products, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Psychology Department staff head count and course enrollment, 1968 - 1970; F-52-3-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Registration system; data element dictionary, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Regional Colleges - enrollments, 1969 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Requirements and prerequisites in each department, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Research semester, a listing for spring, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Sabbatical leaves - costs and eligibility dates, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Royal Roads - pay and benefits questionnaire, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Statistics requests, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Students - new and returning by academic year to, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Student Society resolutions, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Summer session enrollments, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Teaching Assistant head count for Grad. and Undergrad. TA's, 1970 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - TA's salary totals (semesters 68-2 to 69-1), 1968 - 1969; F-52-3-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - TA total expenditures by semester, 1967 - 1969; F-52-3-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Teaching staff head count, 1965 - 1969; F-52-3-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Listing of regular reports prepared by university with info re name of report, prepared by/for, elements etc., 1970; F-52-3-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - University Data needs, 1969 - 1970; F-52-3-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - University year systems - a bibliography, 1970; F-52-3-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - University of Victoria enrollment statistics, 1967 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - UBC enrollment statistics, 1968 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Surveys and questionnaires - a listing, 1971; F-52-3-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Simon Fraser Student Statistical Analysis Fall, 1965; F-52-3-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 52-6)
  - Selected university statistics for use by the Ad-hoc Resource Allocation Committee, 1975; F-52-3-0-0-80 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Enrollment and participation statistics, 1966 - 1976; F-52-3-0-0-81 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Paper re basis for determining non-academic staffing needs in academic departments. (source?), 1975; F-52-3-0-0-82 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Citizenship statistics for students, fall, 1972; F-52-3-0-0-83 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Graduate Student Statistics, 1965 - 1977; F-52-3-0-0-84 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Alumni Employment Survey, 1969; F-52-3-0-0-85 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Tuition Fees, 1969 - 1971; F-52-3-0-0-86 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Undergraduate Instructional Facilities, 1976 - 1986; F-52-3-0-0-87 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Gross Grade Point Average Report, 1966; F-52-3-0-0-88 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Examination of Projected Enrollment, 1976 - 1985; F-52-3-0-0-89 (Archival box - small 52-7)
  - Enrollments, 1992 - 1993; F-52-3-0-0-90 (Archival box - small 52-7)
- Analytical Studies publications, 1973 - 2001; F-52-4; 37 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by the Analytical Studies office. Series includes publications regarding enrollment and attrition, grading, instructional activities, faculty, University facilities, and other matters. Series also includes various editions of the Fact Book published by the office to answer commonly asked questions about SFU activities and conditions.
  - Resource Implications of New Courses, 1977; F-52-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Post-Secondary Enrollments in the 80's, 1979; F-52-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Undergraduate Course Grades Awarded at Simon Fraser University, 1973 - 1979; F-52-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Analysis of Instructional Activity Data 1978-1979, F-52-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Undergrad Course Enrollment Attrition at SFU 1978-3, 1979-3, F-52-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Analysis of Instructional Activity Data 1979-80, 1980; F-52-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - The Demand for and Supply of Highly Qualified Manpower in Canada in the 1980s, F-52-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Fact Book, 1st Ed., 1980; F-52-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - A Moveable Equipment Identification and Inventory System at SFU, 1980; F-52-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Classroom Utilization 1980-3, 1982-3, 1981 - 1982; F-52-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Analysis of Instructional Activity Data 1980-81, 1981; F-52-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Fact Book, 2nd Ed., 1981; F-52-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Faculty Profile Data Book, 1st Edition, 1982; F-52-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Space Inventory and Entitlement, F-52-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Analysis of Instructional Activity Data 1981/82, 1982; F-52-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 52-8)
  - Fact Book, 3rd Edition, 1982; F-52-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Activity Indices for Academic Departments, 1982; F-52-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Financial Fact book, 1st Ed., 1983; F-52-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - The Impact of S.F.U. on the Economy of the G.V.R.D., 1983; F-52-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Predictors of Undergraduate Academic Success of S.F.U., 1983; F-52-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Analysis of Instructional Activity Data, 1982/83, 1983; F-52-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Fact Book, 4th Ed., 1983; F-52-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Analysis of Instructional Activity Data, 1983/84, 1984; F-52-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Fact Book, 5th Ed., 1984; F-52-4-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Alumni Survey, 1985; F-52-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 52-9)
  - Analysis of Instructional Activity Data, 1984/85, 1985; F-52-4-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 52-10)
  - Historical Distribution of Undergraduate Grade Awarded at S.F.U. 1974/75 to 1984/85, 1985; F-52-4-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 52-10)
  - Fact Book, 6th Ed., 1985; F-52-4-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 52-10)
  - Fact Book, 7th Ed., 1986; F-52-4-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 52-10)
  - Fact Book, 8th Ed., 1987; F-52-4-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 52-10)
  - Fact Book, 9th Ed., 1989; F-52-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Fact Book, 11th Ed., 1990; F-52-4-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Publications, 1991; F-52-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Academic Experience of Undergraduate Students at SFU, 1993; F-52-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Fact Book, 13th Ed., 1993; F-52-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Fact Book, 14th Ed., 1994; F-52-4-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Fact Book, 15th Ed., 1995; F-52-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Undergraduate student surveys, 1995 - 2001; F-52-4-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 52-20)
  - Newsletters, 2000; F-52-4-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 52-20)